Okay, Trap Stars and Trap Starrettes.
I've been being shadow banned like a mug, but I'm here.
So tomorrow, I am doing the live stream performance of What Would the Ancestors Say?
What Would the Ancestors Say is my...
What Would the Ancestors Say is the book version of my one-woman show.
And I appreciate you guys who are going to be there in LA for the show.
Because I'm really excited to bring you the show with new staging, with new writing,
and with just an expanded understanding of the themes and topics.
And we've got a lot going on in this world right now.
We have to really try to keep up and keep track.
Look at this shadow ban.
I have 85 people watching a live.
85?
Yo.
They are on me.
Hey, Emma.
Look at it.
Just dropping, dropping, dropping, dropping.
Fascinating how they really do be shadow banning me like a mug.
So anyways, thank you all for being so supportive and for continuously showing up.
They are trying to shut me down in Seattle, but hopefully I will still see you all there
on my mission-driven book tour.
So make sure you go to AmandaSeals.com for information on when I'm coming to a city near you.
So I will be in Seattle on Monday.
I will be in Detroit on Tuesday.
And I will be in Chicago on Wednesday.
And I want to shout out everybody who came to San Diego last night because it was so beautiful
and so dope.
Thank you, DJ Nilo.
He said, everybody go, went to the event, and SD showcases the power of performing arts
as a medium of education.
That means so much to me.
Yeah.
Go to AmandaSeals.com and it has all the info for all the cities of where I am going to
be doing the events.
I do not have it memorized.
So when y'all are like, where is it at?
I don't know.
I genuinely don't know.
Where'd you come from?
Tyrese.
So I'm really happy that people were happy last night in terms, and happy is a weird
word, but I'm really, I'm really proud to make work that people feel is valuable to their
continued effort to move through.
And one of the biggest things that people are really not able to understand is how much we
have been propagandized and PSYOP'd.
And if you, man, if you knew how much they've been taking from us, then you would really like
understand how much you deserve.
And that's what I'm really trying to get us to see in a much greater way, you know?
Thank you, Party Flag Raids.
And there's a lot of just mayhem and cray-cray that be happening that takes us off our square.
So we got to stay on it.
And this piece, this work, this, this focus is to really try to restore the binds and the
bonds between us as we watch the tethers and bonds between like these United States wither
in front of us.
We are in such a unreal time.
Ain't nobody, y'all don't feel that?
She just feel like surreal.
I mean, sometimes like, what's, what's, what's, what's, what's, what's, what's, what is, what's,
what's, what's, what's, what's, what is, what, what, what, what is going on?
So my book will be available on my website at 9 a.m.
But I would also love for you all to consider getting tickets to the show tomorrow night to
watch on the live stream.
And, um, we're going to be joined by CropSwap LA at the top of the show to talk about the
work that they're doing around food sovereignty and trying to, yes, you can absolutely get the
book in Australia around food sovereignty and around community, uh, building and finding
ways to actually build our, I mean, actually like work our own land, bringing that agrarian-ness
into the mix.
No, the book is not on Audible yet.
That's a whole other thing coming.
That's a whole other phase of work, y'all.
Let me tell you one thing you learn when you are, um, no, the in-person tickets are sold
out.
So we're just selling live stream tickets.
One thing you learn when you are doing self, um, publishing is just how many steps, okay?
How many steps are involved in everything?
So, um, appreciate y'all.
And thank you for joining this live that they are trying to hate on.
And I will see you tomorrow on the stage.
I'll tell you about the book, but we got a lot of time.
I'll tell you about the book another day.
I'm so tired.
Okay.
This is, I'm going to, I'm going to read the back of the book for you.
If you called on your ancestors, what would they think about the current state of the world?
Artistic intellectual Amanda Seals has got some ideas.
Originally created as a theatrical piece on the page, what would the ancestors say is
a genre, is a genre innovating treat that takes on the written form of a high vibrational social
media scroll.
Ms. Seals definitely packages dense content into compact contexts through a variety of
creative methods.
Moving seamlessly in and out of standup comedy, characters, lecture, dialogue, and prose, Ms.
Seals answers questions like, how did Clarence Thomas become a villain?
What does Palestine have to do with black Americans?
Are you the type that Harriet Tubman would shoot if she came back?
And more.
Its lessons are enhanced by intricate illustrations, an inspiring forward, and an additional resources
list that readers, list for readers to further expand their knowledge of the work's themes.
Come through the portal with us, and engage in philosophical thought about the black American
past and present, and imagine the actualizing of a new future.
Pop, pop.
There you have it.
Everyone, have a good night.
Mwah.